<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mansiones_Locura</string>
    <string name="lblPasillo">Corridor</string>
    <string name="lblSotano">Cellar</string>
    <string name="lblLaboratorio">Laboratory</string>
    <string name="lblCocina">Kitchen</string>
    <string name="lblRecibidor">Hall</string>
    <string name="lblJardin">Garden</string>
    <string name="lblHabPrincipal">MainRoom</string>
    <string name="lblHabInvitados">GuestsRoom</string>
    <string name="lblSalaRitual">SorceryRoom</string>
    <string name="txtlblVida">LifePoints</string>
    <string name="txtlblTurno">Turns</string>
    <string name="txtlblAction">Action</string>
    <string name="txtlblAccion">Action</string>
    <string name="lbltxtVida" />
    <string name="lbltxtTurn" />
    <string name="lbltxtAccion" />
    <string name="StartGame">Start Game</string>
    <string name="History1"><b>The story till now ...</b>.\n The office is inundated by smoke snuff. There are several files lining the walls, and wearing the leg of a cheap wooden desk pokes a lot of stacked magazines. Behind the desk there is a bald, chubby man in a state of uncontrollable nervousness\n -. I was waiting for it - says while drumming his fingers on the table \n. - Time is money, and we are losing baskets. Our partner has disappeared, and I need your help to find him. The man throws a young researcher with a manila folder rather dirty \n -. His name is Walter Lynch. He has always been the brain of the company, and without him we will soon go under. Long time no answer our letters, and all our investigations have been ... - pauses, searching for the right word \n - ... unsuccessful. This report contains everything we know about the topic -. Continues, pointing to the folder with the look \ n - Guess what has become of him and bring him back. There is much more at stake than you imagine. \n Later on, in the car, the boy carefully opened the grimy folder. Inside are drawn map with directions to a mansion located on the outskirts of Arkham, Massachusetts. The drawing is quite rudimentary, as if it had been maken by a child. In addition to the map, found a page torn from what appears to be a diary. \n "June 8, 1928. It has been almost a year since the disease took my son. Doctors were puzzled and not enough to understand what it was that gradually consumed his flesh was. I have always been a man of action, and I refused to stay idle while my sole heir withered arms. I spent nine months traveling the world in search of a cure, inquired everywhere, from the heart of the forests to the wisdom of the Far East, the more I found nothing. I continued searching, getting further into smaller unknown places and beyond. I witnessed many mysteries and horrors, but the cure always eluded me. Little did I suspect that it was too late; my poor son died while exploring over the world. He died, and his father was not with him to comfort him in his last moments. I returned home with my wife Edith, with the intention of staying there forever. We mourn our son. Gradually, life returned to normal and I return to work. I started a new business, and my fortune increased as my soul languished. It was not easy to overcome the loss of my son, but I discovered that comfort my poor Edith helped me ignore my pain "On the other side of the page is a note, shorter. "January 21, 1919. How could this happen? Why me? I tried to protect myself. I tried to protect my family, but there was nothing to do. Oh, Edith, you're all I have left. Why did that happen to you? I must further deepen. I will leave no stone unturned, however serious the consequences. I must find an answer! "\n\n\n</string>
    <string name="Start">Start</string>
    <string name="btnExpltxt">Explore</string>
    <string name="hint1">On the operating table lies the bloody body of a man. Around him are willing rusty surgical instruments and rudimentary tools. \n There is one skinned man without lips springs that might be a dire warning while dropping a small silver key ...</string>
    <string name="continar">Continue</string>
    <string name="hint2">Your sight gets blurred and you fall off to the ground, crushed by a sudden vision. In it, a man whistles a happy tune while dragging the lifeless body of a woman by the floor. You shudder when he is taking the body to the outside, in heavy rain and passes it over a muddy puddle. The vision ends with the image of a shovel descending rapidly towards his head ...</string>
    <string name="hint3">You get assaulted by a vision of Walter helding a session of spiritism to communicate with her dead son, \n you watch how a spirit takes this opportunity to get into the mind of Mr. Lynch, forcing him to a single will: \ n \ "Get more souls \ ".</string>
    <string name="itemGoMap">Map</string>
    <string name="itemExit">Exit</string>
</resources>